Michael Brombach

Warren, Michigan | (248) 275-9114 | mbrombach@yahoo.com

Summary

Passionate and detail-oriented Cook with more than three years of experience in the food service industry. Self starter, team player and multitasker who focuses on consistently providing a superior and memorable dining experience.

Skills

Food processing and presentation, strong knife skills, food safety and sanitary practices, speed and accuracy, time management, multitasking, inventory management, organization, attention to detail, written and verbal communication, problem solving, training, critical thinking, MS Office

Experience

AMROCK LLC, Senior New York Specialty Coordinator

Detroit, MI | August 2020 - September 2022

- Part of a specialized team that processed residential refinance loans in New York state
- Achieved Senior status after only 6 months by demonstrating consistent quality and efficiency
- Worked closely with lender clients in a fast-paced environment where attention to detail is required, becoming the go-to team member whenever clients had issues or questions
- Quickly entrusted with training other team members due to thorough knowledge of processes and regulations
- Consistently achieved 200%-400% percent of production goal
- Received multiple "Amaze" awards from team members and leaders for outstanding achievements

GREAT HARVEST BREAD CO., Kitchen Lead

Birmingham, MI | April 2019 - March 2020

- Oversaw daily kitchen operations in a busy bakery, including tracking orders and managing store inventory
- Quickly promoted from baker to kitchen lead and keyholder
- Managed and trained a team of bakers and assisted employees with their duties when needed
- Set the schedule for every day to ensure effective time management
- Laid off due to the COVID-19 pandemic

THE BARKSHIRE, Facility Attendant

Troy, MI | April 2018 - March 2019

- Maintained a clean, safe and caring environment for canines in daycare and overnight boarding situations
- Provided outstanding customer service to pet-parent clients
- Trained new employees and specialized in working with special-needs dogs

BRUEGGER'S BAGELS, Bakery Team Member

Royal Oak, MI | November 2017 - April 2018

- Provided exemplary customer service to patrons while ensuring order accuracy
- Followed all health code requirements to ensure the safe preparation and handling of food

APPLEBEE'S, Line Cook

Madison Heights, MI | February 2016 - July 2017

- Meticulously prepared high-quality meals while following all company and state health and safety guidelines
- Trained new employees and efficiently juggled multiple tasks while ensuring a safe and sanitary working environment for all employees

Education

Oakland Community College

Associate in Arts (in progress), January 2019 - present